<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="hood1title">Step 1: Remove the filters</string>
    <string name="hood2title">Step 2: Clean the filters</string>
    <string name="hood3title">Step 3: Inside of the hood</string>
    <string name="hood4title">Step 4: Outside of the extractor</string>
    <string name="hood5title">Step 5: Dry and place the filters</string>

    <string name="hood1text">First, you must remove the filters from the hood to be able
        to clean them in depth and access the interior to eliminate the remains of grease
        that may have accumulated over time. They are shaped like a metal mesh and are
        usually held by a tab and are quite easy to remove. </string>
    <string name="hood2text">Immerse the filters in a bowl with hot water, soap and a
        degreasing product for at least an hour to soften the dirt that has accumulated in the grilles.
        Otherwise, if you prefer to use homemade products you can add lemon juice or white
        vinegar that are also very effective. When time has elapsed, rub vigorously with a
        cloth or scourer until all the grease is removed and then rinse them thoroughly with
        plenty of water.</string>
    <string name="hood3text">Disconnect the power supply before starting and use a cloth
        soaked in warm water, soap and degreaser. Rub the entire surface carefully to avoid
        doing so on the engine and then, with a clean cloth, rinse and remove the soap.</string>
    <string name="hood4text">The process is the same as for the interior area but it\'s
        recommended that if you are not sure of the right products for the device, use
        only soap and water to prevent the material from being affected or damaged.</string>
    <string name="hood5text">Make sure you dry all the parts well, it is important to
        prevent fungi from forming or a musty smell. In addition, it is best to do
        it with paper towels, especially outside to remove watermarks. Once all the
        parts of the extractor hood have been cleaned and dried, it is time to place
        the filters, just reassemble them and make sure that the flange has fitted well.
        Ready, like new!</string>

    <string name="hoodtips">The motor of a cooker hood is a small induction coil motor,
        which requires next to no maintenance at all. Yet, the motor won’t perform well
        if you haven’t changed or cleaned your cooker hood filter in some time. Steam
        and vaporized grease can pass through dirty filters into the motor directly,
        causing it to cease working. Therefore, the trick to a long-lasting cooker
        hood motor is proper filter maintenance.</string>
</resources>