<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="stove1title">Step 1: Gas stove grates</string>
    <string name="stove2title">Step 2: Wipe grease from stovetop</string>
    <string name="stove3title">Step 3: Spray with vinegar</string>
    <string name="stove4title">Step 4: Coat with baking soda</string>
    <string name="stove5title">Step 5: Brush and wipe</string>

    <string name="stove1text">Remove the stove grates to access the entire stovetop.
        So, you can start with deep cleaning. The stove grates become oily and dirty,
        which is difficult to clean. You may soak the grates into a warm water and soap solution.
        Let it soak for 15-20 minutes. The grease should come off by then, or you may scrub
        it to get rid of the remaining grease. Take some vinegar on tissue paper. Then,
        rub the tissue paper on the stove grates to remove grease from hidden edges.</string>
    <string name="stove2text">Cover the burner with a plastic bag, it makes sure no liquid
        solution gets into the holes in your stove. Now wipe off those extra greases and
        debris with a damp cloth or microfiber towel. You may take a little amount of soap
        into the towel.</string>
    <string name="stove3text">Take vinegar into a spray bottle and spray vinegar over the
        greasy part of the cooktop. Spray all over the greasy marks. Now cover all the
        sprayed areas with tissue papers. Make sure the tissue paper is thoroughly wet.
        You may spray some more vinegar on it to ensure it is wet. Leave the tissue paper
        for about an hour and let it soak. It will help to loosen baked-on grease. Now rub
        all this tissue paper over the stovetop.</string>
    <string name="stove4text">Sprinkle baking soda on the stovetop. Focus on the parts which
        have more grease and still rust. Then spray vinegar over the baking soda. Combining
        both makes the tough stains softer. Both will react, which is normal. It will take
        a few minutes to collapse the tougher scorch marks.</string>
    <string name="stove5text">Now take a non-abrasive brush or use the abrasive side of the
        sponge to rub. The abrasive side of the sponge will not be too harsh on the baked-on
        gas stovetop. Brush the surface gently until you get rid of the remaining rust and grease.
        Finally, take a soft microfiber towel to wipe your gas stovetop. Wipe it until your gas
        stovetop looks clean and shiny like before. Make sure you do not damage any metal parts
        while cleaning.</string>

    <string name="stovetips">Note that consistency is the name of the game. You need to take a
        couple of minutes every day to clean your gas stovetop. It will save the most time. From
        now on, you can cook on your gas stove without worrying about baked-on grease.</string>
</resources>