<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="bathroom1title">Step 1: Shower head</string>
    <string name="bathroom2title">Step 2: Curtain or doors</string>
    <string name="bathroom3title">Step 3: Dingy grout</string>
    <string name="bathroom4title">Step 4: Bathroom tile, walls, and ceilings</string>
    <string name="bathroom5title">Step 5: Toilet</string>
    <string name="bathroom6title">Step 6: Bathroom sink</string>
    <string name="bathroom7title">Step 7: Bathroom vent</string>
    <string name="bathroom8title">Step 8: Cleaning tools </string>

    <string name="bathroom1text">Pour an ample amount of white vinegar
        into a plastic grocery bag (enough to fully submerge the shower head nozzle) and
        tie it in place for an overnight soaking. Remove it in the morning and run the
        water to rinse.</string>
    <string name="bathroom2text">Give plastic shower curtains and liners a spin in the
        washing machine with your regular detergent and a few old towels, which help scrub
        away soap scum and mildew. Rehang to dry.\n\n
        For shower doors, make a paste by adding a few drops of distilled white vinegar to
        a cup of baking soda; apply it directly to the door. Let sit for an hour, then rub
        with a microfiber cloth. Rinse and buff dry with a fresh, dry microfiber cloth.</string>
    <string name="bathroom3text">Dip a grout brush in straight bleach and scrub any discolored areas;
        rinse well. Be sure to ventilate the room. Seal grout every six months to help prevent
        moisture and grime from infiltrating.</string>
    <string name="bathroom4text">Spray tile, countertops, walls, and the ceiling with all-purpose
        cleaner and turn on the shower, cranking the hot water until steam builds (about five minutes).
        Turn off the water, shut the door on your way out, and let the steam and the cleaner mix for
        20 minutes. Then wipe down all surfaces with a clean cloth. To reach high spots, use a clean,
        dry microfiber mop. Wipe the tile floor, too, but only after you’ve finished the rest of the dirty work.
        To minimize water marks on ceramic tile, apply a coat of car wax once a year. Water will
        bead up and roll off. Mildew-resistant paint can also help on untiled walls and ceilings.</string>
    <string name="bathroom5text">Pour a cup of baking soda into the bowl. Let sit for a few minutes;
        brush, and flush. Still seeing spots? A damp pumice stone is abrasive enough to remove lime
        scale and mineral deposit stains but gentle enough not to damage surfaces. In cases of
        extreme grime buildup (or acute toilet-crevice trepidation), invest in a small, light-duty
        electric pressure washer. It lets you blast hard-to-reach areas, like the spots where the
        hinges meet the seat, from a safe distance. Start on the lowest setting—you’ll be amazed by
        what comes out.</string>
    <string name="bathroom6text">Pour white vinegar or baking soda down the drain and flush with hot water.
        For the faucet, use disposable disinfecting wipes, which significantly reduce bacteria.
        (In contrast, cloths may just move germs from one spot to another.) If you must use cloths,
        be fastidious about where each one is employed and stored. When the handles are done,
        floss the faucet (yes, you read that right). The stringy stuff is perfect for tackling
        that narrow, grimy space where the base of the faucet and the taps meet the sink.</string>
    <string name="bathroom7text">First flip the circuit breaker. Then remove the cover and soak
        it in warm water and dish soap. Use the vacuum’s nozzle attachment to get gunk off the
        fan blades; wipe with a damp cloth. Remove dust from the motor and other nooks and crannies
        with a stiff, clean paintbrush, and suck up the debris with a vacuum. When it’s completely
        dry, replace the cover. Later, put the fan on a switch timer (an easy job for a handyman),
        and run it during every shower and for 30 minutes afterward to keep moisture (and energy
        use) in check.</string>
    <string name="bathroom8text">Tackle the toilet brush itself, which you should clean after every use.
        Here’s how: Secure the brush handle between the already-cleaned seat and the basin so that it
        hovers over the bowl; pour bleach over the bristles. Let stand for a few minutes, then douse
        with a pitcher of clean water. Next, fill the brush canister with warm, soapy water and let sit;
        dump the dirty water into the toilet.</string>

    <string name="bathroomtips">Tip 1: Rule #1 for keeping your bathroom clean? Keep it dry—so as
        you\'re cleaning, make sure you dry all surfaces well afterward.\n
        Tip 2: Close the lid of the toilet when you flush, and use the vent fan (it sucks up bacteria
        before they can settle). If you’re not already storing toothbrushes and contact lenses inside
        the medicine cabinet, start now. </string>
</resources>