<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="dishes1title">Step 1: Rinse</string>
    <string name="dishes2title">Step 2: Fill sink</string>
    <string name="dishes3title">Step 3: Soak silverware</string>
    <string name="dishes4title">Step 4: Clean to dirty</string>
    <string name="dishes5title">Step 5: Soak more silverware</string>
    <string name="dishes6title">Step 6: Rinse again</string>

    <string name="dishes1text">Rinse the dishes and stack them in piles.  Use a
        long handle scrub brush and clean large food particles off of dishes.</string>
    <string name="dishes2text">Wipe out the sink and rinse it. Plug the drain.
        Add about two teaspoons of dish soap right under where the water is
        going to hit. Fill the sink about 1/3 with hot water. You want hot water,
        because hot water cuts oils.</string>
    <string name="dishes3text">Place all the silverware in the soapy water to one side.
        Place 4-6 plates in the water (or more if you have a large sink). Then lay in
        as many glasses as you can get in on top of that. Do this so the plates and
        silverware can soak while you are washing the glasses.</string>
    <string name="dishes4text">You\'re going to be using the same tub of soap water
        to scrub the whole sink of dishes, so it\'s important to clean the cleanest
        things first. Generally this means glasses, dishes, pots and pans. You need
        to use a little common sense here. Sometimes the order will vary depending
        on what\'s been cooked. Oily dishes use the most soap power and should go last.</string>
    <string name="dishes5text">Keep placing more dirty dishes in the sink to soak as you
        have room. If the water starts getting gooky then change it.</string>
    <string name="dishes6text">Rinse each piece with running hot water. Turn the water
        on and off as you rinse each piece, so you use very little water. Also, don’t fill
        the sink too full of soapy water when you start. That way, as you go along,
        the rinse water you use keeps your soapy water hot and refreshed.</string>

    <string name="dishestips">Tip 1: Dishwashing will be harder for you later if you let oatmeal cake onto your bowl now.
        Right after eating, scrape whatever solids are left into the trash, including napkins. If there’s still
        gunk on your plates, rinse them off, using a blast from the spray function if you have it.\n
        Tip 2: People often fill one sink with water to rinse dishes but, if you think about it, after the first glass
        or two, the rinse water has soap in it and is recontaminating each subsequent piece. There is a reason why
        surgeons wash their hands in running water and the same principle applies to dishes.</string>
</resources>