<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="windows1title">Step 1: Remove dirt and dust</string>
    <string name="windows2title">Step 2: Optional: make homemade glass cleaner</string>
    <string name="windows3title">Step 3: Spritz generously</string>
    <string name="windows4title">Step 4: Use a microfiber cloth</string>
    <string name="windows5title">Step 5: Skip the squeegee</string>

    <string name="windows1text">Sweep dirt from the window frame with a brush or vacuum it
        up with your machine\'s dusting attachment. This will prevent dirt from turning into
        a muddy mess when mixed with a cleaner. If your window screen looks especially grimy,
        pop it out and wash with hot, sudsy water and a soft brush, then rinse and let dry
        before putting it back. For quickly dusting shades and blinds, it is recommended
        to go over both sides with a microfiber duster or opening the slats and going over
        each one with a damp cloth and followed by a dry one.</string>
    <string name="windows2text">Combine 2 cups of water, 1/2 cup white or cider vinegar and 1/4
        cup rubbing alcohol (70% concentration) and pour them in a spray bottle. Write the
        ingredients on the outside of the bottle for safety.</string>
    <string name="windows3text">Don\'t hold back on the spray, especially if your windows
        look extra dirty. You need plenty of cleaner to dissolve and suspend the dirt so it
        can be completely wiped away — skimp and you\'ll be seeing streaks.</string>
    <string name="windows4text">Some folks like drying panes with newspaper, but you\'re
        better off reusable microfiber cloths. They are super absorbent, washable, and leave
        the glass shiny and streak-free. If you rather use paper towels, choose a brand that\'s
        up to the task. Weak paper towels can shred and leave lint behind.</string>
    <string name="windows5text">Professional window cleaners swear by them, but you have to
        know how to use them right. You squeegee down and where does the water go? On the floor.
        Because of the potential mess and drip factor, try to avoid using squeegees, especially
        for small panes, but they can be more helpful on bigger, picture windows.</string>

    <string name="windowstips">Tip 1: Always clean windows on a cool day out of direct sunlight to avoid streaks.\n
        Tip 2: You only need to clean your windows once or twice a year, but it\'s even easier if you divide the
        job up and do it room by room. \n
        Tip 3: When you\'re cleaning, wipe one side of the window horizontally and the other vertically. If any
        streaks do form, you\'ll easily know whether they\'re on the outside or the inside.</string>
</resources>